# Tony **Egan**

## **Product Designer**

https://tonesdesigns.com tony8egan@hotmail.com +353-86 208 6905

#### **About Me**

Hi, my name is Tony and I'm a designer from County Clare in Ireland. I've worked in the tech industry for over 5 years in support and customer success roles which has given me strong experience engaging, understanding, and empathising with users. I'm passionate about designing functional, aesthetic, and inventive experiences. In September I completed a Master of Science in Interaction and Experience Design at the University of Limerick and received a 1st class honours.

## **Skills & Tools**

Communication Figma Wireframing Sketch **Prototyping** Adobe XD Sketching **HTML** Storyboarding **CSS** Web Design **JavaScript UI** Design Java User Research C++ **User Testing** Arduino Participatory Design Salesforce **Programming** SQL

Information architecture Adobe illustrator
Jira Adobe Photoshop

#### **Interests**

Technology Automotive Golf Music Film Architecture

### **Education**

University of Limerick

Master of Science

Interaction and Experience design

2010 - 2014 University of Limerick

**Bachelor of Science** 

Multimedia and Computer games development

## **Experience**

2015 - 2020

Upland Altify - Dublin, Ireland

Implementation Manager
Tech support engineer

At Altify I supported customers that used the Altify B2B software tools which were native in Salesforce. I worked directly with the engineering and product teams to escalate issues and communicate product enhancement requests. My support role consisted of educating users on how to use the tool, creating new customisations to fit their use cases, triaging, and reporting bugs, and managing a daily support stand up meeting. I also designed, built, and maintained web pages which were used for distributing technical documentation with customers. I then moved on to work as an implementation manager where I would work with new and existing customers to understand their requirements and fit the application to their needs.

2015 - 2015

AIB - Dublin, Ireland

Application support engineer

At AIB I worked between the development team and security team to ensure that the main tool they used worked efficiently and effectively.

2015 - 2015

3 Networks - Limerick, Ireland

Call centre support

At 3 I responded to customer network, device and billing queries and helped customers with their issues.

Clarion resort - Ocean City, Maryland, USA

Housekeeping assistant

At the Clarion I worked with the housekeeping team to stock the supply rooms.

2013 - 2013

2014 - 2014

Beckman Coulter - Clare, Ireland

IT Support technician

At Beckman Coulter I worked with the IT support team to respond to general hardware and software issues on site.